Nguyen Minh Kiet

Junior Frontend Developer

J 0337760892

■ minhkiet78py@gmail.com

facebook.com/pheo.chy.336

github.com/minhkiet78

♦ gitlab.com/minhkiet78py

SUMARY

I'm a web developer with over 1 years of experience. I love to learn new things, especially related to frontend or backend stacks. In the coming time, I will try my best to put myself at a higher level and contribute to the development of the company

Target: Fullstack Developer

EDUCATION

Posts and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Major: Software technology 2018 – 2023

SKILLS

★ Frontend skills: ReactJs · VueJs · Redux/Vuex · Jquery · Typescript · Javascript/ES6 · Bootstrap HTML · SCSS/CSS

Backend skills: Express/Node JS · RestfulAPI · MongoDB · SQL

Soft skills: Work independently Communication · Time management · Logical ability

Others: Data Structure and Algorithm · Git · Postman · Figma

■ English · Read and write documents

EXPERIENCE

IRACE JOINT STOCK COMPANY

Working time

Ho Chi Minh 7/2022 - Now

1. DAI-ICHI LIFE - CUNG ĐƯƠNG YẾU THƯƠNG 2023

• **Description**: A website organizing running and sports events as well as online fitness activities for the community is being organized by Dai-ichi Life Vietnam (DLVN).

- Team size: 4 Dev
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, Laravel, PHP, Boostrap3, MySQL
- Responsibility: Develop Frontend
 - + Built reusable components and an internal shared component library
 - + Convert from Figma to HTML/CSS
 - + Participated in discussions and analysis with relevant parties to clearly defined requirements
 - + Design a responsive website for the mobile version and cross-browser
- Link website: https://cungduongyeuthuong.dai-ichi-life.com.vn

2. App Livefit

- **Description**: Irace's number one online platform for sports training
- Team size: 3 Dev
- Technologies: Vue Js, Javascript, SCSS, Boostrap5, Laravel, MySQL
- Responsibility: Develop Frontend
 - + Build a website from scratch
 - + Built reusable components and an internal shared component library
 - + Working with Tester to fixbug
 - + Design a responsive website for the mobile version and cross-browser
- Link website: https://app.livefit.vn

3. AddMe.vn

- Description: A website that enables users to create personal information based on template designs
- Team size: 3 Dev
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, PHP
- Responsibility: Develop Frontend
 - + Add sample templates to the website
 - + Substitute user data into the template returned from the backend
 - + Design a responsive website for the mobile version and cross-browser
- Link website: https://addme.vn

DAT VIET TECHNOLOGY SERVICES COMPANY

Ho Chi Minh 3/2022 - 7/2022

Working time

1. Gas sales management system.

- **Description**: A website that manages a nationwide gas distribution store
- Technologies: ReactJs, SCSS, Redux, Javascript, React-Bootstrap, NodeJs, MongoDB
- Responsibility: Develop Frontend
 - + Participated in discussions and analysis with relevant parties to clearly defined requirements + Develop old feature and build new function in project
 - + Using api work with Backend
 - + Working with Tester to fixbug

• Link website: http://donhangdev.crmdvs.vn

FREELANCE WORK

Working time 10/2022 - 12/2022

1. E-commerce website

• **Description**: A website that sells shoes

• Technologies: HTML, Css, Bootstrap, Javascript

• Team size: 2 Dev

• Responsibility: Develop Frontend

+ Convert from Figma to HTML/CSS

+ Build the basic functions of the project

+ Design a responsive website for the mobile version and cross-browser

PROJECT

1. Polo store

- **Description**: A website that specializes in selling polo shirts
- Technologies: ReactJs, Express/NodeJs, Restful API, MongoDB, Bootstrap5
- Team size: 1 Dev
- **Responsibility**: Fullstack
 - + Create a base source for the project
 - + Analyze requirements and write basic design documents
 - + Provide API for frontend
 - + Building User-Side Interfaces and Functions
- Link Github: https://github.com/minhkiet78/Polo_Store

2. Music web

- **Description**: A website to listen to music
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Team size: 1 Dev
- Responsibility: Develop Frontend
 - + Analyze and develop user-friendly functions for a music listening app
 - + Design a responsive website for the mobile version and cross-browser
- Link website: https://minhkiet78.github.io/music_player

HOBBIES

- Play sport: soccer, voleyball, chess, swimming, joging
- Listening to music.
- Traveling.